typeinternational.com 2018-05-15

# Privacy | Type International

## Privacy

**Welcome to Typeinternational.com (the “Site”).**

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.  
This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by Typeinternational.com (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

We will never ask personal information in regards to personal information other than Name and Email. We will never share this information with any other parties. You information is safe with us.

**What organizations are collecting the information?**

The only other organizations that will collect information from you are  
1.) Pay Pal to process your payment. Pay Pal is a secure well known pay service.  
2.) The IRS will be the only organization that will ever ask for your Social Security Number. We link you directly through to them as so no other parties will get this information.  
3.) Clickbank will need basic information such as name and address and is also a secure service.

Typeinternational.com has done everything to assure you that your privacy and information is completely safe.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**

Personally Identifiable Information collected is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of Type International and Typeinternational.com except for use as indicated above.

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?**

We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure.
